<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
<modDesc descVersion="">
    <author>Realismus Modding</author>
    <contributors>theSeb, Rahkiin, reallogger, mrbear</contributors>
    <version></version>

    <title>
        <en>Seasons</en>
        <fr>Seasons</fr>
        <de>Seasons</de>
        <es>Seasons</es>
    </title>

    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[Winter is coming... and spring, summer and autumn too.
The Seasons mod changes the fundamental way to play Farming Simulator by introducing seasons and changing all aspects of the gameplay, such as weather, growth, economy, vehicle maintenance and husbandry to suit. 

Experience the trials and tribulations of a real life farmer worrying if you will get all your crops planted on time before it gets too cold, or too dry, for them to germinate and whether you will complete the harvest before the rainy days of autumn when crops will be wet. 

Beautiful visuals to suit the seasons, such as the birth of life in spring, the richness of colour of autumn and bare trees on a bleak winter's day when you are clearing the snow, or doing forestry, will help to fully immerse you in this new environment.  

We strongly recommend that you start your Seasons experience on a brand new save game. Please note that this released version of the mod is not compatible with any previous incomplete versions. Delete the incomplete version of the mod, install this release version and start a new save game.

Alt + S : Seasons menu (growth overview and settings)
Alt + F : Show / Hide weather forecast
Alt + R : Maintain vehicle (must be done when vehicle is parked by a workshop and is only possible when maintenance is necessary)
Alt + N : Skip night (only available once it gets dark, before midnight)

For further info on game play checkout the Seasons section of the in-game help. A full list of features can be found in the mod's readme file and on our website. 

        ]]>
        </en>
        <fr>Seasons</fr>
        <de>Seasons</de>
        <pl><![CDATA[
        Nadchodzi zima... i wiosna oraz lato i jesień.
Mod Seasons zmienia podstawowy sposób gry w Farming Simulator wprowadzając pory roku i zmieniając wszystkie aspekty rozgrywki, takie jak pogoda, wzrost roślin, ekonomia, obsługa maszyn oraz zwierząt w pasującą całość.

Doświadcz problemów i trosk z życia prawdziwego farmera obawiającego się czy zdąży posiać wszystkie uprawy zanim zrobi się za zimo lub za sucho, aby wykiełkowały oraz czy uda się zakończyć żniwa przed jesiennymi deszczami, kiedy zboża zamokną.

Piękna szata graficzna wpisująca się w pory roku, taka jaka rozkwitające wiosną życie, bogactwo kolorów jesienią oraz nagie drzewa w ponury zimowy dzień, kiedy zajmujesz się odśnieżaniem lub pracą w lesie, w pełni pozwolą Ci się wczuć w nowe środowisko.

Zdecydowanie zalecamy rozpoczęcie przygody z modem Seasons na nowym zapisie gry. Uwaga: ta wersja modu jest niekompatybilna z wcześniejszymi nieukończonymi wersjami. Należy skasować wcześniejszą nieukończoną wersję, zainstalować tą i rozpocząć nową grę.

Alt + S : Menu modu Seasons (zestawienie wzrostu upraw i ustawienia)
Alt + F : Wyświetlenie / Ukrycie prognozy pogody
Alt + R : Przegląd pojazdu (wykonywalny tylko dla pojazdu zaparkowanego w warsztacie oraz możliwy jedynie gdy przegląd jest wymagany)
Alt + N : Pominięcie nocy (dostępne tylko wieczorem, przed północą)

Więcej informacji o grze z modem Seasons znajduje się w menu pomocy gry. Pełna lista funkcjonalności dostępna jest w pliku readme oraz na naszej stronie internetowej.
        ]]>
        </pl>
        <es><![CDATA[Seasons es un mod que, como bien indica su nombre, simula las estaciones añadiendo sus características y un punto más de realismo al juego.]]></es>
    </description>

    <iconFilename>icon.dds</iconFilename>

    <multiplayer supported="true"/>

    <l10n filenamePrefix="translations/translation"/>

    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="src/loader.lua"/>
    </extraSourceFiles>

    <inputBindings>
        <input name="SEASONS_SHOW_WF" category="ONFOOT" key1="KEY_lalt KEY_f" key2="" button="" device="" mouse=""/>
        <input name="SEASONS_REPAIR_VEHICLE" category="ONFOOT" key1="KEY_lalt KEY_r" key2="" button="" device="" mouse=""/>
        <input name="SEASONS_SHOW_MENU" category="ONFOOT" key1="KEY_lalt KEY_s" key2="" button="" device="" mouse=""/>
        <input name="SEASONS_SKIP_NIGHT" category="ONFOOT" key1="KEY_lalt KEY_n" key2="" button="" device="" mouse=""/>
    </inputBindings>

    <storeItems>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="resources/fakeStoreItem/item.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="resources/fakeStoreItem/item2.xml"/>
    </storeItems>
</modDesc>
